[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the next number in this sequence: 4, 6, 8, 9, 10, 12, 14, 15, 16, 18, 20?", "correct_answer": "21", "incorrect_answers": ["23", "22", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 2004 movie is this audio clip from?", "correct_answer": "Meet the Fockers", "incorrect_answers": ["Father of the Bride", "American Wedding", "Surviving Christmas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which novel by Scottish writer Robert Louis Stevenson is set during the War of the Roses?", "correct_answer": "The Black Arrow", "incorrect_answers": ["The Master of Ballantrae", "Strange Case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde", "Treasure Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fear of high objects, drafts, and air-swallowing is known as rhodophobia.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to extract superior espresso consistently, you must precisely control many factors. Which of the following is not one of those factors?", "correct_answer": "Fat content of milk you use", "incorrect_answers": ["The tamping pressure to press the coffee grounds into the portafilter", "The fineness of the grind", "The amount of coffee grounds you use in each dose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of Jack-Jacks babysitter in the Academy Award-winning film The Incredibles?", "correct_answer": "Kari", "incorrect_answers": ["Karla", "Kathy", "Karen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress starred alongside Tobey Maguire as Mary Jane Watson in the 2007 movie Spider-Man 3?", "correct_answer": "Kirsten Dunst", "incorrect_answers": ["Natalie Portman", "Keira Knightley", "Scarlett Johansson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is Pancetta?", "correct_answer": "bacon", "incorrect_answers": ["sausage", "milk", "small pepper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long can a total lunar eclipse last?", "correct_answer": "1 hour  40 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["4 hours  30 minutes", "2 hours  30 minutes", "3 hours  20 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is how long it took the Internet to attract 50 million users.", "correct_answer": "4 years", "incorrect_answers": ["20 years", "10 years", "5 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Dr. Marvin on the way back home from the institution in What About Bob?, after he dumps Bob off and strands him in the middle of nowhere?", "correct_answer": "all of these", "incorrect_answers": ["His car tire gets punctured.", "He gets a speeding ticket.", "A vehicle drives by and splashes mud all over him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Cocktail, it is revealed that Jordan is going to have twins.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]